Lewes
You're back
Sit down and eat
Did Daniel
give you your share
He made over 3 million this year
How much did you get
Was it 1.5 million
It was Daniel's idea after all
He should take the lion's share
Is it 1 million then
He said it would be fifty-fifty
Now it's not even 1 million
How much did he actually give
500,000
That's fine
We'll get more later anyway
Every little bit adds up
50,000
That's just to pay us back
The farm's profits
have nothing to do with us anymore
That's not what he said back then
If he hadn't suggested a partnership
would you have worked so hard
This is a scam
Daniel
How could he do this
That ungrateful wolf
I'm going to find him
Don't go
Arguing won't help
You're his brother-in-law
How could he cheat his own family
Enough
These past two years
just think of it as Lewes helping Daniel
In the future
There won't be a future
I used that 50,000
to rent a farm across from Daniel's
I also borrowed 40,000
You invested it all
What if you lose it
Then we lose it
Lewes
I know you have a plan
Since you've decided
then do it right
Still short on cash
I need another 30,000
With that 30,000
I can upgrade the water filtration system
to the best one
Survival rates will rise by 30%
Here is 25,000
Take it for now
We'll figure out the rest
Dad
Mom
This is the money you and Mom
saved over a lifetime
I can't
Take it
What's this
This is what I saved
from odd jobs nearby
It's not much
Only 6,328
Please use it
I thought
you didn't support me
We're a family
Just do what you want to do
If it all fails, we'll go find jobs
But
I believe in my man
Dad
Mom
Cynthia
I will definitely succeed
I'll make them regret it
and shut up